A Guide to the Mary Blanton Easterly Papers, 1877-2006 (bulk 1900-1945)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Mary Blanton Easterly Papers, 1877-2006 (bulk 1900-1945)
The Library of Virginia
43509, 44141
18 cubic feet (43 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Augusta National Golf Club files are closed until 2038.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mary Blanton Easterly, Richmond.
Biographical Information
Mary Friend Blanton was born in Richmond, Virginia on 20 November 1923. She was the daughter of Dr. Wyndham Bolling Blanton (1890-1960) and Natalie McFaden Blanton (1895-1987). She attended St. Catherine's School in Richmond, and Converse College in Spartanburg, South Carolina. On 28 August 1943, Blanton married Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr. (1922-2005). They had two sons and three daughters.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1877-2006, of Mary Blanton Easterly (b. 1923) of Richmond, Virginia, including correspondence, subject files, scrapbooks, memoirs, books and other publications, ephemera, and oversize items. The bulk of the collection covers the years 1900 to 1945.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Correspondence.
II. Subject Files.
III. Scrapbooks.
IV. Memoirs.
V. Books and Publications.
VI. Ephemera.
VII. Oversize Items.
VIII. Augusta National Golf Club Files (RESTRICTED).
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence, 1900-2006., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 1-18)
  The correspondence covers the years 1900-2006, but the bulk of it dates from 1937 to 1945. Subjects include attending summer camps in West Virginia, student life at Converse College and the Virginia Military Institute, social life, visits with family and friends, courtship, marriage, and raising children. There is information concerning activities in Richmond during World War II, and a good deal of corrrespondence between Easterly and her husband while the latter was stationed on Iwo Jima and Okinawa. The later letters in the collection deal with trips abroad, and also relate to Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr.'s interest in golf.
  Chronological.
  - 1900-1919. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1920-1929. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1930-1936. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1937 (July). (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1937 (August-December). (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1938 (January-July). (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1938 (August). (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1938 (September-December). (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1939 (January 1-15). (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1939 (January 16-31). (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1939 (February). (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1939 (March). (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1939 (April). (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1939 (May). (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1939 (June). (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1939 (July 1-10). (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1939 (July 11-20). (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1939 (July 21-26). (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1939 (July 27-31). (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1939 (August 1-10). (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1939 (August 11-20). (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1939 (August 21-31). (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1939 (September). (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1939 (October). (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1939 (November). (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1939 (December). (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1940 (January). (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1940 (February). (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1940 (March). (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1940 (April-May). (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1940 (June). (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1940 (July 1-10). (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1940 (July 11-18). (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1940 (July 19-24). (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1940 (July 25-31). (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1940 (August 1-5). (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1940 (August 6-10). (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1940 (August 11-14). (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1940 (August 15-31). (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1940 (September 1-15). (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1940 (September 16-30). (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1940 (October 1-7). (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1940 (October 8-20). (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1940 (October 21-31). (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1940 (November 1-13). (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1940 (November 14-25). (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1940 (November 26-30). (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1940 (December). (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1941 (January 1-11). (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1941 (January 12-18). (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1941 (January 19-31). (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1941 (Februart 1-15). (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1941 (February 16-28). (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1941 (March 1-15). (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1941 (March 16-31). (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1941 (April 1-15). (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1941 (April 16-30). (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1941 (May 1-15). (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1941 (May 16-31). (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1941 (June). (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1941 (July). (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1941 (August). (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1941 (September 1-7). (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1941 (September 8-11). (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1941 (September 12-17). (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1941 (September 18-24). (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1941 (September 25-30). (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1941 (October 1-5). (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1941 (October 6-10). (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1941 (October 11-17). (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1941 (October 18-24). (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1941 (October 25-31). (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1941 (November 1-5). (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1941 (November 6-13). (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1941 (November 14-25). (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1941 (November 26-30). (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1941 (December 1-4). (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1941 (December 5-7). (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1941 (December 8-31). (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1942 (January 1-6). (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1942 (January 7-12). (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1942 (January 13-18). (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1942 (January 19-24). (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1942 (January 25-31). (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1942 (February 1-7). (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1942 (February 8-11). (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1942 (February 12-15). (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1942 (February 16-19). (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1942 (February 20-23). (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1942 (February 24-28). (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1942 (March 1-6). (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1942 (March 7-10). (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1942 (March 11-15). (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1942 (March 16-21). (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1942 (March 22-25). (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1942 (March 26-31). (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1942 (April 1-10). (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1942 (April 11-15). (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1942 (April 16-20). (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1942 (April 21-30). (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1942 (May 1-6). (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1942 (May 7-31). (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1942 (June). (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1942 (July). (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1942 (August). (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1942 (September 1-15). (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1942 (September 16-21). (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1942 (September 22-30). (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1942 (October 1-8). (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 1942 (October 9-17). (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1942 (October 18-31). (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 1942 (November 1-5). (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1942 (November 6-13). (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 1942 (November 14-20). (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 1942 (November 21-30). (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 1942 (December 1-12). (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 1942 (December 13-31). (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 1943 (January 1-14). (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 1943 (January 15-20). (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1943 (January 21-31). (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 1942 (February 1-7). (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1942 (February 8-12). (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1942 (February 13-24). (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1942 (February 25-28). (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1942 (March 1-4). (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1942 (March 5-8). (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1942 (March 9-12). (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1942 (March 13-16). (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1942 (March 17-19). (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1942 (March 20-25). (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1942 (March 26-31). (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1943 (April 1-5). (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1943 (April 6-13). (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1943 (April 14-25). (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1943 (April 26-30). (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1943 (May 1-5). (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1943 (May 6-10). (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1943 (May 11-14). (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1943 (May 15-22). (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1943 (May 23-31). (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1943 (June). (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1943 (July 1-5). (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1943 (July 16-31). (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1943 (August 1-15). (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1943 (August 16-31). (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1943 (September 1-12). (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1943 (September 13-30). (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1943 (October). (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1943 (November). (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1943 (December). (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1944 (January). (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1944 (February). (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1944 (March). (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1944 (April). (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 1944 (May). (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1944 (June). (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1944 (July). (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1944 (August). (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1944 (September). (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1944 (October). (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1944 (November). (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1944 (December 1-18). (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1944 (December 19-25). (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1944 (December 26-31). (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1945 (January 1-7). (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 1945 (January 8-14). (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 1945 (January 15-23). (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 1945 (January 24-31). (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1945 (February 1-10). (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1945 (February 11-16). (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1945 (February 17-28). (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1945 (March 1-7). (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1945 (March 8-17). (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1945 (March 18-25). (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1945 (March 26-31). (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1945 (April 1-10). (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1945 (April 11-19). (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 1945 (April 20-23). (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 1945 (April 24-30). (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 1945 (May 1-7). (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1945 (May 8-18). (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1945 (May 19-31). (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1945 (June 1-7). (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 1945 (June 8-16). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 1945 (June 17-24). (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1945 (June 25-30). (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - 1945 (July 1-7). (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 1945 (July 8-18). (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 1945 (July 19-24). (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 1945 (July 25-31). (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 1945 (August 1-8). (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 1945 (August 9-15). (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1945 (August 16-24). (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1945 (August 25-31). (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1945 (September 1-10). (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 1945 (September 11-19). (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 1945 (September 20-30). (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 1945 (October 1-8). (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 1945 (October 9-31). (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1946-1949. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - 1950-1956. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 1957-1959. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1960-1969. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1970-1989. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 1990-2006. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - n.d. (Box 18, Folder 4-9)
- Series II. Subject Files., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 19-26)
  The subject files include accounts and receipts, announcements, artwork, awards and honors, certificates, clippings, diaries and medical notebooks kept by Dr. Wyndham Bolling Blanton while he was stationed in France during World War I, genealogical notes on the Armistead, Blanton, Bolling, Crouch, Friend, McFaden, Temple, and Wallace families, golf publications, greeting cards, invitations, a 1917 journal and photograph album of Harry Watkey Easterly, Sr., while he was in Russia on business, information relating to ladies member/guest activities at the Country Club of Virignia, memberships, newsletters, a notebook kept by Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr. while he was stationed on Iwo Jima and Okinawa, photographs, poetry, programs, materials related to the Virignia Military Institute, including information on the reinstatement of married cadets following World War II, and other items.
  Alphabetical.
  - Abstracts of Letters. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Accounts and Receipts. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Agreement - Mineral Lands in Goochland County. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Announcements. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Artwork. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Awards and Honors. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Baby Care Instructions. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Blanton Forum - Virginia Historical Society. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Books and Articles. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Certificates. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Clippings - Appointments, Awards, Honors. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Clippings - Books and Authorship. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Clippings - Clubs and Social Events. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Clippings - Engagements and Weddings. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Clippings - Football, Track and Field. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Clippings - Golf. (Box 19, Folder 16-19)
  - Clippings - History and Historic Preservation. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Clippings - Medicine. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Clippings - Miscellaneous. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Clippings - Obituaries. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Clippings - Politics. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Clippings - Presybterian Church. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Clippings - Speeches. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Converse College. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Country Club of Virginia - History. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Customs List. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Diaries and Medical Notebooks, 1915. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Easterly Family Bible Record. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - First Presbyterian Church (Winchester). (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fitzgerald, Isabel A. - House Sale (4103 Sulgrave Road). (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Garden Book - Cherokee Road House. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Genealogical Notes - Blanton. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Genealogical Notes - Easterly. (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
  - Genealogical Notes - Tighe. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Genealogical Notes - Miscellaneous. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Golf. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Golf Articles By and About Harry W. Easterly, Jr. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Golf Publications. (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Golf Scorecards. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Greeting Cards. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Historic Preservation and Historic Richmond Foundation. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Invitations. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Harry Watkey Easterly, Sr. - Petrograd, Russia - 1917. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Ladies Member/Guest - Country Club of Virginia. (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
  - Memberships. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Nolley's School - Certificates of Distinction, 1900-1901. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Notebook - Football. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Notebook - Okinawa and Iwo Jima. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Nothing Much" Thank You Notes. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Obituaries of Harry W. Easterly, Jr. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Photographs. (Box 23-24)
  - Photograph Album - Camp Easterly, Poqouson River, 1919. (Box 25)
  - Photograph Album - Russia, 1917. (Box 25)
  - Poetry and Verses. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Programs. (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
  - Ration Books. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Record of the Hampden-Sydney Alumni Association. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Remarks at Reception Honoring Mary B. Easterly, The Library of Virginia, 26 March 2009. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Report Cards. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - St. Catherine's School. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - St. Stephen's Church. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - School Debate Notes (Monopolies). (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - School Exercises - Biology Notebook. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - School Yearbooks and Annuals Entries. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook - Natalie Blanton 90th Birthday, 1985. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Second Presbyterian Church (Richmond, Va.). (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Sympathy Cards. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Valentines. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Military Institute. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Military Institute - Football Game Programs. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Military Institute - Re-Instatement of Married Veterans. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Military Institute - "The Turn-Out". (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Vistor's Log, 1918-1920. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Will of Natalie McFaden Blanton, 1977. (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Series III. Scrapbooks.., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 27-34)
  There are fourteen scrapbooks contained in the collection that were presented to Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr., on the occasion of his 60th birthday in 1982, as well as a scrapbook (ca. 1930-1945), kept by Mary Blanton Easterly. The volumes include brochures, certificates, clippings, correspondence, invitations, greeting cards, photographs, programs, and ephemera. For preservation purposes, they have been disassembled.
  - Volume 1. (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
  - Volume 2. (Box 27, Folder 5-8)
  - Volume 3. (Box 28, Folder 1-7)
  - Volume 4. (Box 28, Folder 8-10)
  - Volume 5. (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
  - Volume 6. (Box 29, Folder 5-9)
  - Volume 7. (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
  - Volume 7. (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - Volume 8. (Box 30, Folder 4-6)
  - Volume 9. (Box 30, Folder 7-9)
  - Volume 10. (Box 30, Folder 10-13)
  - Volume 11. (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Volume 12. (Box 31, Folder 5-9)
  - Volume 13. (Box 31, Folder 10-11)
  - Volume 13. (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
  - Volume 14. (Box 32, Folder 5-7)
  - Scrapbook, ca. 1930-1945. (Box 33, Folder 1-9)
  - Scrapbook, ca. 1930-1945. (Box 34, Folder 1-6)
- Series IV. Memoirs., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 35-37)
  Easterly wrote her memoirs, and they were published in November 2008 under the title "M.E. and sometimes H.E.: Before I Forget What I Know." This series contains typewritten drafts of the various chapters, with handwritten corrections, as well as supporting documentation, photographs, and other material. A signed copy of her published memoirs is also included.
  - "M.E. and sometimes H.E.: Before I Forget What I Know" - Chapter Drafts, Corrections, Supporting Documentation, and Inscribed Final Copy. (Box 35-37)
- Series V. Books and Publications., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 38-40)
  A portion of the correspondence between Easterly and her husband, written between 1940 and 1945, as well as some of her husband's 60th birthday scrapbooks, were also published, and copies are contained in this series. There are numerous other books and publications as well, many of them were written by Natalie McFaden Blanton (1895-1987), including, "A Little More," "B.R. to N.B.," "Hopping, Skipping, and Jumping," "Long Ago," "Let's Not Be Grave," "Love Remains," "Miss Jennie and Her Letters," "Ninety-Nine Notes to Love Remains," "Nothing Much," "Poems for Christmas," "The Door Opened," and "West Hill, Cumberland County, Virginia: The Story of Those Who Have Loved It." Also contained in this series is Dr. Wyndham Bolling Blanton's three-volume history of medicine in Virginia.
  - Books and Publications. (Box 38-40)
- Series VI. Ephemera., Extent: 1 box. (Box 41)
  There is one box of ephemera which includes patches, track and field ribbons and medals, and notecards relating to a genealogical research project by Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr.
  - Ephemera. (Box 41)
- Series VII. Oversize., Extent: 1 box. (Box 42)
  The oversize items include many of the same types of material found in the Subject Files, including articles, certificates, genealogical charts, newsletters, newspapers, and photographs.
  - Articles. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Certificates. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Class Photographs. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Genealogical Charts. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Genealogical Charts, Aerial Photographs, Golf Course Plans. (Map-case 10, Drawer 13)
  - Golf Scorecard. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Ladies Guest/Member - Country Club of Virginia - Fabric Swatches. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Memories of George H. Fulton, Jr.. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Menu - Restaurant Girardet, Crissier, Switzerland. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers/Newsletters. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Plat - Waller Gold Mine Company (Goochland County). (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Resolution - Death of Harry Watkey Easterly, Jr.. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Rifle Practice Targets. (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Series VIII. Augusta National Golf Club Files (RESTRICTED)., Extent: 1 box. (Box 43)
  There is one box of material relating to the Augusta National Golf Club, including a draft and final version of "Inside the Masters: Green Jackets and Green Olives," by Mary Blanton Easterly, published in 2008 by Tabby House. Also included is correspondence and a photo album. This series is closed until 2038.
  - Draft and final version of "Inside the Masters: Green Jackets and Green Olives," correspondence, and photo album. (RESTRICTED). (Box 43)